sourcegraph.com 2019-11-10

# Sourcegraph Privacy Policy

Last modified: September 26, 2019

Sourcegraph, Inc. ( **"Sourcegraph," "we," "our,"** or **"us"** ) understands that privacy is important to our online visitors to our Sourcegraph.com website and users of our online services (collectively, for the purposes of this Privacy Policy, our **"Website"** ), as well as users of our private or self-hosted Sourcegraph instances (collectively with our Website, our **"Service"** or **"Services"** ). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information that we collect through our Service. By using our Service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.

Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service.

## Data controller

The Data Controller for Sourcegraph and our Services is:

Sourcegraph, Inc.   
142 Minna Street, 2nd Floor, San Francisco, CA 94105

## What types of information do we collect, and for what purpose

The categories of information we collect can include:

  * **Information you provide to us directly:** We may collect personal information such as a username, first and last name, email address, and payment information, when you register for a Sourcegraph account, participate in forums, comment on blog posts, submit a feedback survey, or if you correspond with us.

  * **Information we collect from third parties and social media sites:** We may collect information about you from third-party services. For example, we may receive information about you if you interact with our site through various social media, for example, by logging in through or liking us on Facebook or following us on Twitter. The data we receive is dependent upon your privacy settings with the social network. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Service.

We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features of the Services. We may use this information to communicate with you, such as to send you email messages, and to follow up with you to offer news and information about our Services. We may also send you Service-related emails or messages (e.g., account verification, change or updates to features of the Services, technical and security notices). For more information about your communication preferences, see "Your Choices About Your Information" below.

## How we use cookies and other tracking technology to collect information

### Usage information from private or self-hosted Sourcegraph instances

Sourcegraph collects aggregate and high-level information about usage from self-hosted Sourcegraph instances through a server ping. The server ping sends a payload containing data such as total number of users and whether certain features are enabled or in use.

The only personal information collected is the email address of the initial Sourcegraph installer and site admin (or, if that user is deleted or demoted to not be an admin, the first such active site admin). This information allows us to contact the technical administrator of the Sourcegraph instance to deliver information about product updates and policy changes, and for customer development purposes. Other than the initial site admin email address, only aggregates of usage data are sent: no usernames, user emails, user personal information, code, repository names, file names, URLs, or other such private content is sent to Sourcegraph.

### Information from Sourcegraph.com visitors

We and our third-party partners may automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit or use our Website.

  * **Cookies**. For instance, when you visit our Website, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Website (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click, how frequently you access the Website, and other actions you take on the Website), and allow us to track your usage of the Website over time.

  * **Log file information**. We may collect log file information about your browser or mobile device each time you access the Website. Log file information may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, information about your mobile device, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Website, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

  * **Email beacons**. We may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Website.

  * **Web analytics**. We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Website. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other information that assists us in analyzing and improving the Website.

Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our Users, we are not able to respond to Do Not Track signals from your browser at this time.

We may use the data collected through cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data, and clear gifs information to:

  1. remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site;
  2. provide custom, personalized content and information;
  3. provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Website;
  4. monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, usage, and demographic patterns on our website and our Service;
  5. diagnose or fix technology problems; and
  6. otherwise to plan for and enhance our service

### Third-party services and data processors

We use third-party automated devices and applications, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate usage of our Website. Google Analytics is a Web-based analysis tool provided by the Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, USA. Google provides further information about its own privacy practices and offers a browser add-on to opt out of Google Analytics tracking at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

We use third-party applications such as Google Apps, HubSpot, GitHub, Slack, DocuSign, and more to track and manage conversations, chats, or email exchanges with our users and customers. These products and companies provide further information about their own privacy practices on their websites.

We use third-party applications such as Google Cloud Platform, Honeycomb, and more to host, serve, store, and analyze our Website's operational infrastructure and operational data collected on our Website. These products and companies provide further information about their own privacy practices on their websites.

We use third-party applications such as Stripe and Xero to manage corporate billing and invoicing. These companies provide further information about their own privacy practices on their websites.

We and our third-party partners may also use cookies and tracking technologies for the purpose of tracking the effectiveness of our own ads placed on Google, Twitter, etc. on Sourcegraph.com (never on private or self-hosted instances). For more information about tracking technologies, please see “Third party tracking and online advertising” below.

## Bases for processing your information

**Performance of a contract:** The use of your information may be necessary to perform the contract that you have with us. For example, if you use our Website to purchase Sourcegraph product subscriptions or services, create a profile, post and comment through our Website, or request information through our Website, we will use your information to carry out our obligation to complete and administer that contract or request.

**Legitimate interests:** We use your information for our legitimate interests, such as to provide you with the best content through our Service and communications with users and the public, to improve and promote our products and services, and for administrative, security, fraud prevention, and legal purposes.

**Consent:** We may rely on your consent to use your personal information for certain direct marketing purposes, such as sending you newsletter updates about Sourcegraph products. You may withdraw your consent at any time through the unsubscribe feature provided with each marketing email or by contacting us at the addresses given at the end of this Privacy Policy.

## Sharing your information

We may share your personal information in the instances described below. For further information on your choices regarding your information, see the "Your Choices About Your Information" section below.

We may share your personal information with:

  * Other companies owned by or under common ownership with Sourcegraph. These companies will use your personal information in the same way as we can under this Privacy Policy;

  * Third-party vendors and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, as needed to carry out their work for us, which may include data hosting, billing, payment processing, or providing analytic services;

  * Other parties in connection with a company transaction, such as a merger, sale of company assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event of a bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings; and

  * Third parties as required by law or subpoena or to if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law, legal process and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Sourcegraph, our Users, or others.

We may also aggregate or otherwise strip data of all personally identifying characteristics and may share that aggregated or pseudonymized data with third parties.

Any information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Website becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings. If you remove information or content that you posted to the Website, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Website, or if other Users have copied or saved that information.

### Third Party Tracking and Online Advertising

We participate in interest-based advertising and use third party advertising companies to serve you targeted advertisements based on your online browsing history and your interests. We permit third party online advertising networks, social media companies, and other third party services, to collect information about your use of our Service over time so that they may play or display ads for our products on other websites, apps, or services you may use and on other devices you may use. Typically, though not always, the information used for interest-based advertising is collected through cookies or similar tracking technologies. We and our third party partners use this information to make the advertisements you see online more relevant to your interests, as well as to provide advertising-related services such as reporting, attribution, analytics and market research.

To learn more about interest-based advertising and how you may be able to opt-out of some of this advertising, you may wish to visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>, and/or the DAA’s resources at www.aboutads.info/choices. You may also be able to set your browser to delete or notify you of cookies by actively managing the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please note that some advertising opt-outs may not be effective unless your browser is set to accept cookies. Furthermore, if you use a different device, change browsers or delete the opt-out cookies, you may need to perform the opt-out task again.

You may also be able to limit certain interest-based mobile advertising through the settings on your mobile device by selecting “limit ad tracking” (iOS) or “opt-out of interest based ads” (Android).

**Google Analytics and Advertising**. We may also utilize certain forms of display advertising and other advanced features through Google Analytics, such as Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager Integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. These features enable us to use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick advertising cookie) or other third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and display ads based on your past visits to the Sites. You may control your advertising preferences or opt-out of certain Google advertising products by visiting the Google Ads Preferences Manager, currently available at <https://google.com/ads/preferences>, or by vising NAI’s online resources at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>.

## Global privacy practices

Information we collect will be stored and processed in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy but we understand that users from other countries may have different expectations and rights with regard to their privacy. For all Sourcegraph.com visitors, Website users, and self-hosted Sourcegraph users, no matter their country of location, we will:

  * provide clear methods of unambiguous, informed consent when we do collect your personal information;
  * only collect the minimum amount of personal data necessary for the purpose it is collected for, unless you choose to provide us more;
  * offer you simple methods of requesting access, correction, or deletion your information that we have collected, which we will make reasonable efforts to accommodate; and
  * provide Service users notice, choice, accountability, security, and access, and we limit the purpose for processing. We also provide our users a method of recourse and enforcement.

If you are located in the European Union, you are entitled to the following rights with regard to your personal information and data:

  * Right of access to your personal data, to know what information about you we hold
  * Right to correct any incorrect or incomplete personal data about yourself that we hold
  * Right to restrict/suspend our processing of your personal data
  * Right to complain to a supervisory authority if you believe your privacy rights are being violated

Additional rights that may apply to you in certain instances:

  * Right of data portability (if our processing is based on consent and automated means)
  * Right to withdraw consent at any time (if processing is based on consent)
  * Right to object to processing (if processing is based on legitimate interests)
  * Right to object to processing of personal data for direct marketing purposes
  * Right of erasure of your personal data from our system (“right to be forgotten”) if certain grounds are met

To exercise your privacy rights, you can contact us directly at [support@sourcegraph.com](mailto:support@sourcegraph.com).

## Your choices about your information

**How to control your communications preferences:** You can stop receiving promotional email communications from us by clicking on the "unsubscribe link" provided in such communications. We make every effort to promptly process all unsubscribe requests. For as long as you are using our Services, you may not opt out of Service-related communications (e.g., account verification, changes/updates to our products or features of the Service, technical, and security notices).

**Modifying or deleting your information:** If you already have an account on the Website, you may access, update, alter, or delete your basic user profile information by logging into your account and updating profile settings.

Sourcegraph will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to perform our contractual obligations, provide you services, to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, preserve legal rights, or enforce our agreements.

We will delete inactive accounts and any personal information in them after a period of eighteen (18) months.

If you have any questions about reviewing, modifying or deleting your account information, you can contact us directly at [support@sourcegraph.com](mailto:support@sourcegraph.com).

## How we store and protect your information

**Storage and processing:** Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Sourcegraph or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Sourcegraph or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Keeping your information safe:** Sourcegraph cares about the security of your information, and uses commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. However, no security system is impenetrable and we cannot guarantee the security of our systems 100%. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Sourcegraph will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

## Usage data

Sourcegraph's collection, storage, and use of Usage Data, and our responsibilities with respect to such Usage Data, are set forth in our Terms of Service and are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

## Children's privacy

Sourcegraph does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. If you are based in the European Union, we will not knowingly collect your information if you are under the age of 16. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under 13 or child in the European Union under 16, please contact us at [support@sourcegraph.com](mailto:support@sourcegraph.com).

## Links to other web sites and services

Our Service may integrate with or contain links to other third party sites and services. We are not responsible for the practices employed by third-party websites or services embedded in, linked to, or linked from the Service and your interactions with any third-party website or service are subject to that third-party's own rules and policies.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Service, please contact us at [support@sourcegraph.com](mailto:support@sourcegraph.com).

## Changes to our privacy policy

Sourcegraph may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices. When we do so, we will revise the "last modified" date at the top of this page.
